

Atila Oliveira
Web Developer

Átila Gonçalves Oliveira Júnior

Königsberger nr.7 72414, Rangendingen

0049/157 372 89281 atila.oliveira.jr@gmail.com.com

Portfolio: http://atila-oliveira.developerakademie.com/portfolio

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/atila-oliveira-jr-60869319a/

Github: https://github.com/atilaoliveirajr

About Me

I am a Frontend developer, trained by a professional software development school in Germany. I built Front-End projects alone and in groups that you can find in my public portfolio. I combine my experience in project management in the metallurgical industry with my acquired development skills.

Main Stack:

- TypeScript, Angular
- JavaScript
- HTML, SCSS

Side Stack:

- Java (Spring)
- MySQL

Skills

- **Building Applications with JavaScript** (Web-Applications, Jumpand-Run-Games, Responsive Websites)
- Using Angular to build material design applications (Built a CRM prototype deployed in a databank and my own webpage)
- **Software-Project Management:** Understanding Scrum & Agile Project Management.
- Working in a Software-Team: During learning coding, I did several group projects where I learnt how to develop a software project in a team.
- Other relevant skills: I learnt Java and concepts of OOP as well as SQL and Github.

Professional Experience

Tubex GmBH / Tooling Specialist

NOV 2017 - PRESENT, RANGENDINGEN.

- Strengthen technical communication between the Brazilian and German engineering departments.
- Reporting and assisting the importation of new technologies from one factory to another.

Tubex do Brasil / Process Engineering Leader

JUNE 2013 - OCT 2017, ITUPEVA - BRAZIL

- Managing new product projects to the main clients in the region such as BDF, Unilever and P&G.
- Responsibility in improving the factory efficiency through lean manufacturing principles.

Education

Anchieta University/ Production Engineering

FEB 2007 - NOV 2012, JUNDIAÍ

Developer Akademie / Front-End Developer Ausbildung JavaScript &

Angular Development Training

AUG 2020 - FEBRUARY 2021, MUNICH

Project based coding academy. Main Stack: JavaScript, Angular

Portfolio: http://atila-oliveira.developerakademie.com/portfolio

Extensive Coding School, Learning Front-End Development, Coding, Agile Project Management and building several projects in teams and alone.

Alura / Java: Web Developer

JULY 2019 - JULY 2020, SÃO PAULO

Online lessons where the student have access to the entire platform during a year and can attend the course he wants.

I did the entire Java course that also included Spring, TomCat 9.0, JPA2/Hibernate and Relational Database, further more I attended the following modules: Programming Logic I and II, HTML5/CSS3, Git and Linux Command Line.

Languages

German: Intermediate

English: Fluent

Portuguese: Mother language

References

Junus Ergin (Software Development Coach); <u>junus@developerakademie.com</u>; +49 1573 7033036